

CONTACT

- +971 555991721
- ✓ balasubramani985@gmail.com
- Oubai, UAE

EDUCATION

2003 - 2006 ANNA UNIVERSITY

 Diploma in Electrical and electronics Engineering

SKILLS

- Facility Management
- CAFM
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

DRIVING LICNESE

Valid UAE driving license

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Hindi (Fluent)
- Tamil (Fluent)
- Kannada (Fluent)
- Malayalam (Fluent)

BALASUBRAMANIAN

MEP SUPERVISOR

PROFILE

I am a driven, organized and motivated Maintenance Supervisor with previous work experience in managing facilities, projects, services, operations and personnel. I have expert knowledge of the various issues surrounding facilities including, but not limited to, Health & Safety, risk assessments, site maintenance, building inspections, security and managing contractors. I take great pride in my work and strive to achieve the best possible results at all times.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Farnek Services LLC

2020 - PRESENT

MEP Supervisor

- Supervise daily Facilities Maintenance operations.
- Managed all maintenance including HVAC, plumbing, electrical, fire alarm and firefighting systems, Controls, Carpentry and Masonry, BMS system, building equipment's.
- Perform corrective and preventive maintenance of all HVAC & Electrical equipment's.
- Instruct staff in work policies and procedures, and the use and maintenance of all equipments.
- Manage and maintain all tools and equipment to OSHA standards.
 Keeping track of personnel's working hours and absences Organizing visits and responsible for booking rooms and meetings, Performing regular site inspections
- Holding regular team meetings to ensure everyone is up-to-date with the latest developments in the organization and addressing any issues or concerns.

MEP Supervisor

2014 - 2019

Trojan Holdings LLC

- Ensuring that relevant building maintenance, repairs and services are completed efficiently, on time and budget
- Tracking budgets and ensuring payment is made on time
- Working with a variety of contractors from a number of different sectors to agree and form contracts and agreements
- Managing all security issues at the allocated premises including finding the right security companies, CCTV specialists and guards to protect the premises